[{"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "I say we have a different political system.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "No, because I cannot improve your distinction was so close to (INAUDIBLE).", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Do you see Iran as being in those categories, that you have to get in now because if you leave it and they can protect themselves from air strikes or whatever, it becomes too late?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Our primary concern is that Iran will not be blocked when the time is still there to block them.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Is that your primary concern?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "ARAK: You know, first of all, we are trying to avoid of letting it slip into anything that carries a certain relationship to internal politics into here or in Israel.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "How much does that that factor into your military planning on Israel's behalf that the president of the United States has an election coming in November?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "I don't want to respond to this question.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Are you prepared to act completely unilaterally if you have to?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "I can't say.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "OK, but who would be a higher quality friend come November, President Obama or, potentially, President Mitt Romney, do you think?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "I think it's improper for an Israeli political leader to express a public -- publicly any kind of judgment or even to make remarks.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "You think that whoever -- whoever wins would still be a resolute friend of Israel?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "I think that they have to push harder.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "Shouldn't the international community now be driving as hard against Syria as they did in the Libyan situation?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "It certainly has, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Well, I guess it depends on if she means my mind or my body.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "How do you feel about being called the Hillbilly Orson Welles?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "Was it really?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Well, I mean I was, you know, I'm honored any time anyone talented, you know, says anything nice about me.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "What do you think of that description?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Well, it's certainly not on purpose.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "Do you like being a character of mystique even to your loved ones?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Yes, or some place.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "If you had your way, you'd make them in some underground dungeon inside the house?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Well, no, not so much.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "By being that guy that used to be married to Angelina, as much as everything else?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "Not much lately.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "How could you play baseball with yourself?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Well, you know, that's -- those numbers are assigned to different people in my life through a process that I can't quite explain, but it has to do with my obsessive-compulsive disorder.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "How did she get to be number four?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "Well, I mean I'm not -- I don't really follow, you know, the celebrity news much.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Do you find it odd, the -- the circus that goes with that, the -- the sheer oddity of having somebody so close to you become such a ridiculously famous person?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "-- that's an overstatement, I would say, that -- that I don't follow it.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Do you care, though?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Will you be at their wedding, do you think?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Oh, gosh, no.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Would you feel uncomfortable?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Well, I told her, I said, look, when you think of it this way, this is my longest relationship and we're not married, you know, so it's not real hard to figure out.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "There's some great stuff in the book about -- and you touched on this earlier -- about modern life.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "So I just said let's leave well enough alone, you know?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "I think -- I think we, as a country, are very happy as long as we're comfortable in our own house and our own backyard.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Do you think that enough Americans lead lives of sensible frugality, if you like, who, you know, take personal responsibility?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "It'll come out this fall.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "And when does it come out?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "I guess that would make me feel pretty good.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "ASRY: Look, I think in what we do, or at least what I try to do, really what we're trying to do is generate a return for our investors.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "How do you feel about that and how you trying to change the image, if you are, of hedge funds and hedge fund managers?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Look, I don't know all the details.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "What do you think of what happened to JP Morgan?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "Let's turn to Facebook, a happier story, in many ways, an amazing success story for American capitalism.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "And when you're not, everybody looking at that and says, well, how did you not know that?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "That I don't know.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "Is it worth 100 billion?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "That I honestly don't know.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Is there any way of valuing Facebook really, in any sensible way?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Zero.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "How big of a slice of the Facebook pie are you hoping to carve out for yourself?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Nothing?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "I think what we do is we try to invest in companies that are in trouble.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "ORGAN: Why not?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "I personally don't have an issue in paying higher taxes.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "Are you -- are you prepared to be Buffetted, to be taxed at a much higher level?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "I think it is going to be a difficult election.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "Do you think Obama is going to win easily or does he have a hell of a fight on his hands?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "I think the safe bets are investing in the U.S. Treasuries.", "docId": "120516pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "For everyone in America struggling a bit, but they have a little bit of money to invest, what is the kind of thing you would urge them to consider as a relatively safe bet right now?", "qSentId": 559}]